Thank you for watching!
Well, good morning, everyone!
Good morning.
Very early.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'll start talking and then I'll start messing up.
What's up with that?
We are
We are JoJo Bojo!
I've been itching to do it
I've been itching to do it.
You know...
I've been doing it alone for a long time.
JoJo?
Endex?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's right.
Dio.
Dahl dahl game.
Oooh.
Oh!
I have an announcement.
I don't know much about it.
I'm not familiar with it
I've never heard of it.
What kind of game do you think it is?
What?
No, sir.
It's from the Dar Dar game.
Are you aiming for Tulip's Dahl?
Do, do, do, do, do.
Get to the rhythm.
Dahl.
Dahl dahl
Maal maal maal
I'll say it again and again, here
For example, the convenience store convenience store dahl For example, a convenience store convenience store dahl
The next person who answers
Convenience store darui
I thought it was darui.
So dar is darui.
Is there a different kind of dar?
That's...
It's the way you say it.
It's a way of saying that the dar-dar is...
It's a cushion.
It gives you time to think.
There's a reprieve.
That's why it's not an easy game.
It's not that it's easy, but it's a little bit
It's a little bit
It's a little more than instantaneous.
I've got time to kill.
Dalui!
First of all, it's better to practice slowly
I prefer the attack.
Attack?
It's too...
It's not good for the game.
It's not good for the game, that's for sure.
It's better to play the fun game.
Yeah, I know.
I know that 100% already.
It's fun.
♪ Dar ♪
Dar Dar
# Dar at the convenience store #
~ Dar~
Darl~
# Famichiki's cold #
Darl
Hey, that's not even...
You can't put the name of the product on the package.
On the package. In a package
I'll tell you what the package says.
Doesn't that sound like more fun than I'm having?
Dar.
Doesn't he look like more fun than me?
Dar!
♪ Dar... ♪
Dar
♪ Dar on the train ♪
♪ Darl ♪
Darl
Dar Dar Dar Dar
It's all coming back to me
I like it.
Dar
Darl from the convenience store
Whoa!
Here it comes.
Darl
# Darl #
# The self-checkout inches
# I don't feel good #
# Dahl #
~ Dahl ~ ~ Dahl ~ ~ Dahl ~ ~ Dahl ~ ~ Dahl
# Dahl, the air conditioner #
Huh?
Dahl
Dust.
Self checkout.
I can't decide.
Dar.
Dull. Dar~
Dar~
White,
The first hand.
Mr. Varada.
You care too much.
You're right.
I tend to forget.
I don't doubt it!
Oh, well, let's continue, continue!
Ready, set, go!
Dar, dar, dar, school dar
Dar, dar, the principal's story is so long
Dar, dar, dar, the supermarket sar
Dar, dar, dar.
No fine money at all
It's your fault, it's your fault
Because you didn't bring it to the prevail
Aloha's lax
I'm trying to sort out the super jumped
I'm soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo tired!
let's go, let's go, let's go
Dahl, dahl, dancing dahl
Dar, dar, dar, Skaalen.
That's it?
I'm tired of dancing.
That's right.
Dancing is exhausting.
Then you're not tired.
I'm tired.
I'm tired!
You ready? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Dar, dar, keith dar.
Dar. Dar.
Dar. Dar. Sometimes.
Stiff shoulders, sore back Stiff shoulders, back pain.
Dar Dar
Cooking Dar
Dar Dar Dar
I gotta say it's delicious without being anything like that.
It's good, but it's airy
It's funny.
You got it right Darl Dahl.
It definitely looked a little showbiz.
It's not so much a showbiz thing.
It's more like when it's right in front of you.
When it's right in front of you.
I don't think it tastes like I thought it would.
It's delicious.
It's airy.
That's what I'm talking about, something that doesn't taste so good.
"It's very elegant.
That's what you're saying, right?
The broth has an aroma.
It's long.
Dahl. Dahl.
Dar Dar in the bath.
Dar Dar Dar
I thought it was for hot water
It was water
Dar Dar Dar
Car dahl
Dahl Dahl
Driving a manual car uphill
good
Dahl
Game dahl
Dahl Dahl
Dahl DahlDar Dar
Dar. Dar.
~~
Mystery Box
I'm in the box, I'm in the box, I'm in the box, I'm in the box
Mystery Box Girl
There's no subject.
I'm going back for a second.
I thought it was hot water, but it's water.
It's all his fault.
I'll check it out.
Mental.
I can go aromatic.
It's been a long time.
It's a little weird.
Focus.
I'll answer the questions.
Practice practice practice
Doubtful.
Try
Dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl
My luggage is so heavy it ripped my bag
Dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl
Mom's hair often falls on the floor
Christmas dar dar dar dar
Christmas tree pieces often fall on the floor
Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar
All of it!
Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar
Here it comes!
Oh, shit.
Two quarters, two quarters, something on the floor, something on the floor.
This could be a lot more fun than it sounds.
It's too long!
Then walk away.
I can do this a lot. I can do it a lot. I can do it before you.
I can do it a lot.I can go on and on.
I can go again and again
Dahl Dahl Takuan's Dahl
Dar Dar Dar I've never had much of it, but it looks like it had texture
Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar
Dar Dar Dar I get so much sand in my shoes!
Dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl dahl pencil dahl dahl
Dar Dar Dar Dar Loop silencion dar
I think I got one of these.
Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar Dar
In the end, it's not so much fun, and you tend to get bullied at the end.
Hmmm...
Awwwww!
I think you're talking about something different than I am.
You seem to talk about it differently than I do.
I always say that. Sorry.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, about this, about that.
I'm... I'm kidding. Kidding, kidding, lying, lying.
Joke, joke, lie, lie.
Mistake.
It's better that way.
Wrong.
Awww.
That's something, isn't it?
Also, the whole time
Kai's clapping has been bothering me.
What?
I haven't noticed it at all.
It's gonna beep.
It's gonna make a sound.
I want to do stuff, but you're doing it.
I couldn't help but notice.
It feels like you're tapping, but it's not making a sound.
That's what I'm trying to say.I'll tell you when it's said and done.
Thank you for watching!